<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tatva Events</string>
    <string name="title_activity_events">Events</string>

    <string name="title_section1">Section 1</string>
    <string name="title_section2">Section 2</string>
    <string name="title_section3">Section 3</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_example">Example action</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_event">EventActivity</string>

    <string name="event_item_view_tag">1</string>

    <string name="event_desc_demo">
<hr />
        Tattva Adventures invites you all for Batch 1 of Velas Turtle Festival starting 3rd March, 2017.<br />
<br />
Velas Beach:<br />
Velas beach is the place where this turtle festival will be held. Its a village in Ratnagiri district around 200 km south of Mumbai, leaving no stone unturned to save the turtles from disaster. Ten years ago, before the conservation effort started, most of the Olive Ridley turtle eggs were either consumed by humans, dogs and other wild animals. But with awareness and large-scale participation of locals, 19000 hatchlings have been released in the decade long effort. From the start of the nesting season beginning November, locals maintain a vigil for the female Olive Ridley turtles that come home to nest. Females lay up to three clutches per season, one clutch containing between 90-150 eggs. The eggs, size of ping pong balls, are collected and incubated in a hatchery constructed on the beach by the locals. Each clutch is marked by its date and left to incubate naturally. Let us welcome the tiny Olive Ridley’s during Velas Turtle Festival 2016.<br />
<br />
Bankot:<br />
The name Bankot is derived from “Bavanna Kot” a Marathi phrase meaning fifty-two forts. The Great Shivaji Maharaj captured this tiny fort and added it to Swarajya, which was the fifty second fort and hence the name “Ban Kot”. It is a coastal area on the Arabian Sea with attractive beaches.<br />
<br />
Harihareshwar:<br />
Surrounded by four holy hills Harihar, Harshinachal, Bramhadri and Pushpadri Harihareshwar is a region in Konkan which is amazingly beautiful with hills playing the perfect foil for long stretch of pristine beach. The Harihareshwar temple built in the 16th century with the deities of Vishnu Brahma and Shiva is the primary attraction in Harihareshwar along with beautiful stretch of beach.<br />
<br />
The itinerary for the tour leaving 3rd March, Friday Night :<br />
Meeting Point :Pritam Hotel Dadar East at 11:00 PM<br />
<br />
Saturday<br />
Reach Velas by 05.00am<br />
Get fresh, Visit Velas Beach at 6am for Turtle Festival<br />
Breakfast<br />
Bankot Fort (15 Minutes Trek)<br />
Explore Bankot fort<br />
Return to Velas by 1.30pm<br />
Lunch at Velas (Veg Konkani Food)<br />
Rest till evening<br />
Visit Velas beach for Turtle Festival in the evening at 5pm.<br />
Fun and games to be played at Velas beach<br />
Back to Velas Home Stay<br />
Dinner<br />
Post Dinner we will be having night walk around the village<br />
Retire for the day<br />
<br />
Sunday<br />
Wake up at 5.00 AM<br />
Visit Velas Beach for Turtle Festival in Morning at 6.00 AM..<br />
Have breakfast and Start for Harihareshwar Temple and Beach by Ferry<br />
Lunch at Harihareshwar<br />
Post Lunch , Start our return journey by 3pm<br />
Reach Dadar by 9:30 – 10pm<br />
<br />
Cost for the Tour is 2,300/- per person which includes<br />
Mumbai to Mumbai transportation fare in private (Non-A/c) bus<br />
All Meals (2Breakfast + Tea, 2 lunch, 2 Evening tea and 1 dinner)<br />
Village Homestay And Expertise charges.<br />
(Mineral Water And Cold Drinks not included)<br />
<br />
Registrations are only through phone calls<br />
To Register Call<br />
Shri : 9870 371 280<br />
Jeet : 9220 975 649<br />
<br />
Please transfer full amount to the below bank account to confirm your registration.<br />
<br />
Payment details:<br />
Name of the account: Shrikant Janardhan Shenoy<br />
A/c # 002601534455<br />
IFSC code- ICIC0000026<br />
Bank name: ICICI Bank<br />
Bank Address: Kailash Plaza, Ghatkopar East<br />
<br />
Things To Be carried:<br />
—————————————————————<br />
TORCH V IMP<br />
Identity proof<br />
Winter clothes<br />
Some ready to eat food. Plum cakes, Biscuits etc.<br />
A bottle of water (atleast 2 Ltrs) Compulsory<br />
Medicine those if u require usually (Optional)<br />
A good trekking shoes, extra pair of flotters.<br />
A haversack to put in all the things to be carried….so that one has ones hands free while trekking.<br />
Pleases do not carry Jholas.<br />
Please avoid wearing Jewellery<br />
<br />
Rules<br />
———————————<br />
No Smoking, tobacco and alcohol<br />
Be a group – its not a race<br />
NO littering please…we are educated smile emoticon<br />
<br />
The leader’s decision will be final and binding on all members. No Arguments will be entertained.<br />
<br />
Note–<br />
Please understand this ain’t a picnic, all Trekking and Adventure activities demand fitness.<br />
We request you to get a medical fitness check done before you participate in any such events. If suffering from any allergy carry proper medications and inform your
trek leaders about it. Also make sure you have a sufficient supply of medication for your trip, building in an allowance for any travel delay. Those with Active Chest
and Heart diseases that limit physical activity should not go to high altitudes.<br />
<br />
Regards,<br />
Tattva Adventures<br />
<br />
Jai Hind<br />
<br />
    </string>
</resources>
